Search  Submit

Privacy Policy
==============

[Home](https://www.personally.co.uk/) » Privacy Policy

Who we are
----------

We are Personally (a trading name of theMediaFlow Ltd). We are committed to protecting personal data in compliance with all applicable laws, rules, and regulations.

What personal data we collect and why we collect it
---------------------------------------------------

### Contact forms

We have provided contact forms for you to contact us. We will use the information provided by you only for the purposes of your communication.

### Cookies

We use cookies on our websites. For more information, please see our [cookies information page](https://www.personally.co.uk/cookie-policy/).

### Service Provision

In order to provide our services and contact you, we obviously need a name, email address, password, company name and other such contact details. We will also require invoicing details.

Domain names and privacy
------------------------

Domain names are not personal data, however domain registration information may contain personal data linking you to the domain names you own. We recommend that you check with your registrar regarding their privacy policy or their privacy services.

Who we share your data with
---------------------------

We will not share or sell any personal data with third-parties. Only authorized personnel have access to your information to service your account.

How long we retain your data for
--------------------------------

Whilst you have an account, or as required to provide services to you and to meet legal or regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, prevent fraud and abuse, or enforce our terms and conditions.

Non personal information will be stored on Google Analytics for 26 months.

What rights you have over your data
-----------------------------------

You can request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

If you have an account with us, you can edit your personal account information when logged in.

Where we send your data
-----------------------

No personal information will be sent anywhere. They are stored with 3rd party service providers (hosting, data centers) with whom with have agreements regarding data security.

Your Rights
-----------

* The right to be informed about how your personal information is being used
* The right to access the personal information we hold about you
* The right to request the correction of inaccurate personal information we hold about you
* The right to request that we delete your data, or stop processing it or collecting it, in some circumstances
* The right to stop direct marketing messages and to withdraw consent for other consent-based processing at any time
* The right to request that we transfer or port elements of your data either to you or another service provider
* The right to complain to your data protection regulator

Questions & Contact information
-------------------------------

Feel free to contact us anytime if you:

* Have any questions or feedback about this privacy policy
* Would like us to stop using your information
* Want to exercise any of your rights as set out above, or have a complaint

You can contact us [here](https://www.personally.co.uk/contact-us/) or if you’d like to, you can write to us at:

theMediaFlow Ltd  
co/HSA,  
Lewis House,  
Great Chesterford Ct,  
Great Chesterford,  
Saffron Walden  
CB10 1PF

_Last updated May 2018 to address the European Union General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”), which will take effect on May 25, 2018. This data protection law replaces the 1995 Data Protection Directive (Directive 95/46/EC)._

Personally

_"A dynamic company obsessed with all things related to doing business online"_

Currently spending on online marketing? Contact us for a free no obligation appraisal...

[

](https://www.personally.co.uk/)

©Personally, a brand of theMediaFlow Ltd. All Rights Reserved.

Search  Submit

Welcome to Personally, accept our cookies or customise your journey in settings.

Accept

            Cookie Settings

Close GDPR Cookie Settings

* Privacy Overview
* Strictly Necessary Cookies
* 3rd Party Cookies
* Cookie Policy

Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to provide you with the best possible user experience.

You can adjust all of your cookie settings by navigating the tabs on the left hand side.

Strictly Necessary Cookies

Strictly Necessary Cookie should be enabled at all times so that we can save your preferences for cookie settings.

Enable or Disable Cookies 

If you disable this cookie, we will not be able to save your preferences. This means that every time you visit this website you will need to enable or disable cookies again.

3rd Party Cookies

This website uses Google Analytics to collect anonymous information such as the number of visitors to the site, and the most popular pages.

Keeping this cookie enabled helps us to improve our website.

Enable or Disable Cookies 

Please enable Strictly Necessary Cookies first so that we can save your preferences!

Cookie Policy

More information about our [Cookie](https://www.personally.co.uk/cookie-policy/) & [Privacy](https://www.personally.co.uk/privacy-policy/) policies

Enable All Save Changes
